

Mandarin | English

# Raphael Pang Teng Xuan

www.raphaelpang.com

tengxuanp@hotmail.com (+60)11-10696958 Malaysian

Hi, I am a 25-year-old IT officer/web dev enthusiast with junior level experience as a software developer.

I am looking for Front End developing / UI-UX designing opportunities to sharpen up my web development skills while do my best to help companies to reach their goals.

# **Work Experience**

#### Intretech Malaysia Sdn. Bhd. (2021 - 2022)

IT Assistant Engineer (April 2021 - April 2022)

- IT system maintenance Server backups, user domain/email account management, server & VMs configuration.
- Desktop support Assist organization 's staff by troubleshooting errors regarding hardware.

software, system issues.

Supervisor: IT Supervisor, Mr. Roger Huang Guan Hao (+60)11-51341316

### OCK Setia Engineering Sdn. Bhd. (2020)

Software Developer (May 2020 - Dec 2020) Intern (Jan 2020 - May 2020)

- Design & develop new system modules & enhance existing system modules for the company's ERP system.
- · Maintain organization 's websites.

Supervisor: IT Senior Manager, Ms. Quek Meow Wah

## **Education Level**

### **Bachelor of Information Systems (2017-2020)**

School of Computing & Creative Media, UOW Malaysia KDU University College

# **Key Skills**

#### **Scripting & Programming**

Tailwind CSS | JavaScript | React JS | PHP

### **Graphical Design & UI Design**

Photoshop | Illustrator | Figma | InDesign

# **Certificates & Recognitions**

Advance Employee Year 2021

Intretech Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.

 ISO 27001:2013 Awareness, Implementation & Internal Auditing Training

Intretech Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.